# **Brian Hamburg**

## **SUMMARY**

With over a decade of experience building user interfaces for the Web and providing technical support, my focus has always been to remove friction from the user experience with an appreciation for both accessibility and aesthetics. I strive to create components that are usable and reusable.

Key technologies used include vanilla JS, Vue, Angular, React, jQuery, Sass/CSS, and Bootstrap on the front end; Adobe Experience Manager (AEM) with HTL (Sightly) templates written in Java/Apache Sling on the back end; automated testing with Cypress, Vitest/Vue Test Utils, JUnit, and Jasmine; and Git and Jenkins for CI/CD.

### RELEVANT EXPERIENCE

# The Walt Disney Company

## Senior Software Engineer - Front End / February 2022 - Present

Built and maintained user interfaces with Vue.js for software that controls the content delivery ecosystem for properties including Disney+, ESPN+, and Star+. Implemented new automated testing with Vitest/Vue Test Utils and Cypress.

## American Red Cross

## Full-Stack Developer / February 2021 – February 2022

Maintained and created editable components for the AEM enterprise content management system using HTL (Sightly) templates and contributed to associated APIs for redcross.org and redcrossblood.org. Implemented new automated testing with JUnit, Jasmine, and Cypress.

# Thomas Jefferson University and Jefferson Health

## Web Developer / July 2015 - February 2021

As a member of Jefferson's IS&T department, created and maintained editable web templates and components for public-facing websites built within AEM with HTL (Sightly), server-side JavaScript, and Java. Often contributed to the development of other front-end web applications as needed.

## Front-End Web Developer / September 2012 – July 2015

As a member of Jefferson's marketing team, created landing pages, microsites, WordPress themes, banner ads, and email campaigns for clinical and university clients. Updated existing Sitecore templates for the main hospital website. Redesigned the hospital appointment request form with a responsive layout, enhancing usability and decreasing the abandonment rate. Trained users in WordPress, SurveyGizmo, and MailChimp.

## Law School Admission Council

### **Web Services Specialist** / September 2008 – September 2012

Created and maintained web pages for LSAC.org to adhere to W3C accessibility standards. Converted the intranet portal from a static web site to a Microsoft SharePoint site. Administered WebTrends and Google Analytics on LSAC.org and the intranet portal. Created and maintained online surveys in SurveyGizmo with Salesforce integration.

### **EDUCATION**

Master's Certificate in Application Development / La Salle University / Obtained in 2013

Bachelor of Science in Business Administration / La Salle University / Graduated 2011, Magna Cum Laude

Associate of Arts in Business Administration / Bucks County Community College / Graduated 2010

Associate of Arts in Graphic Design / CHI Institute / Graduated 2006